

A resilient, goal-oriented, efficient and creative individual with excellent coordination and communication skills, which was acknowledged by the manager of former workplace. Formerly worked in O-bank as a department assistant for 10 months before entering MSc Marketing in Durham. Highly engaged in several projects and data analysis in former job. Experienced with multiple culture team working with people from 10+ countries.

YU HSUAN CHEN(Jarita)

Phone:

+44 7467 342557

E-Mail:

chenyouxuan87@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yu-hsuan-chen-180239242

Skill Highlights

- Multitasking
- Efficiency
- Communication Skills
- Data Analysis and Visualization
- Detail-oriented

Languages

Mandarin --- Native

English --- Fluent (IELTS overall 7)

Taiwanese --- Native Japanese --- Basic

German --- Studied

French --- Studied

EDUCATION

2019-2021

Bachelor in Art: Chinese Literature - National Central University, Taiwan

03/2020-09/2020(Cancelled due to Covid-19)
University of Stuttgart
Exchange Student (with scholarship)
Stuttgart, Germany

2022-2023

Postgraduate of MSc Marketing Durham University, United Kingdom

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

11/2021-8/2022

Relation Manager Assistant - O-bank, Taipei

- Responsible for variable data analysis and visualization, gained by SQL, in the Salary Transfer Department.
- Responsible for monthly department Self-Inspection of the Financial Supervisory Commission.
- Supporting the marketing events, such as introducing the latest ESG cards by cooperating with the P+ League basketball Public Relations team.
- Responsible for making weekly working performance PowerPoint.
- Calculating, analyzing and visualizing monthly sales performance by Excel.
- Working on different cases with cross-functional communication.

09/2019-12/2019

Sales and Customer Services-Ming-Ren Leather, Taipei

- Responsible for customer service, such as, introducing our services, delivering their leather goods, and communicating with the workers on phone.
- In charge of developing more customers online by Facebook and Instagram and in person, persuading them to purchase our services.
- Dealing with clients' arguments about the quality of the services.

07/2019-08/2019

Part time assistant-JING-CHI management consulting, Taipei

- Responsible for assignments from the manager.
- Dealing with a government department-Ministry of health and welfare.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

09/2017-06/2018

Chinese Literature Department, National Central University

Public Relation/Leader in cross department events

- Leading PR team and building connections between University and firm
- Holding events for 100+ students from different departments
- Controlling the budget for orientation activities

10/2017-05/2018

Voluntary Works

- Teaching and accompanying elementary students in the morning once a week for 3 months--- Innovated Flipped classroom lectures as a team representative of lecture organizing team.
- Accompanying disabled people after school 4 hours a week for 3 months--- Responsible for accompany projects.
- Helping hearing Impaired person wash cars during their working time.
- Doing volunteer work for the local libraries for 16 hours every year (since 13 years old).

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

- Play table tennis (since 6 years old)
- Play volleyball
- Work out (since 15 years old)

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python (Basic), SQL
- IT: Microsoft words, Microsoft power point, Microsoft excel, Teams, Outlook, Zoom, SEO, SEM

REFERENCES

Department Head of O-Bank